But there's one message you can tell a youth from our life.
How you think creates how you feel.
How you feel becomes an emotion.
That emotion becomes a vibration.
That vibration becomes a magnet that attracts things to you, also repels things away from you.
Only think about what you want.
Forget about what you don't want.
Never speak about what you don't have.
If there's no enemy on the inside of your mind, no enemy on the outside could ever do you or your body any harm.
Don't look out the window.
Look in the mirror.
Fuck what they say.
Fuck how they feel.
Do you do what you want to do and be good at it? Just make sure what you do is good to you and for you